<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>[SYR] Thrumkin</name>
    <author>Syrchalis</author>
    <supportedVersions>
        <li>1.0</li>
        <li>1.1</li>
    </supportedVersions>
	<url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=43449</url>
    <description>Adds a humanoid thrumbo race.
The Thrumkin are a neolithic race that inhabits different planets, having been captured and brought along for the ride due to their rarity and beauty. 

A large, graceful humanoid creature, with long white fur, a large sharp horn and short simple tail. Their striking resemblance to Thrumbos gave them their name and leaves no doubt to where this race might have originated from. 
		
While generally peaceful they make excellent melee fighters, thanks to their resilent hide and razor sharp horn. Thrumkin live in harmony with nature and know more about plants and animals than most advanced cultures, at least on the planet they are living on.

They are not particularly skilled when it comes to building tools and using them, neither are their structures more than simple protection from the elements.

Requires Humanoid Alien Framework loaded before this
Harvest Yield Patch is not required, but highly recommended, otherwise some aspects of the race won't work as I intended them to.

Advantages:
- Durable, taking 20% less damage from all sources
- Can craft crossbows, a slow but accurate medieval weapon
- Powerful melee attack using their horns
- Bonuses to plants and animals
- Resistant against the cold
- Cannot get several annoying traits (Creepy Breathing, Abrasive, Gourmet, Annoying Voice)
- Can be sheared regularly for thrumbo fur
- Good negotiators
- Good with general labor
- Higher foraged nutrition in caravans
- Can eat wood
- High carrying capacity

Disadvantages:
- Chance to get lower quality when crafting/building/scultping
- Care about thrumbos and what you do to them
- Bad handling of guns
- Bad traders
- Gain very little benefit from eating meat
- Have a generally higher appetite
- Get sad when their horn is stolen (=amputated)

Additional feature: Menardy
Menardy is a unique female thrumkin that spawns regularly (not always!) as faction leader for the thrumkin tribe. She has a unique visual appearance and extremely desirable traits and stats (still somewhat randomized). She can be captured and recruited.
    </description>
    <packageId>syrchalis.thrumkin</packageId>
    <modDependencies>
    <li>
        <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
        <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
        <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
	<li>
        <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
        <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races 2.0</displayName>
        <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
        <downloadUrl>https://github.com/erdelf/AlienRaces/</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    </modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
	</loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>